Uh, today's class is really the
objective, let's see, today I'll tell you, today the
idea was from four to six uh
business management systems, the theory, from six
to seven is uh intermodular project.
So, in principle, today's
class is until 7. What happens is
that yesterday I said that what I wanted was to have
the objective of installing Odo and
making some minimal component and that
somehow Fran and Luis when they see
the video and Josué don't know anything, although
well, well, I sent it
to the company anyway.   It
was so that they have the information
to know, in view of the interview with the
internship company, whether they get involved
in Odo's mess or not, okay?  And just a
quick look to see what it looks like
and how to do things
within ODO, right?  Uh, so that's why I
said yesterday that if we had
n't met that goal by 7,
then we would continue until whatever
time was needed, okay?  Since that
objective has been met, well, we'll
finish the 7 now. That said
, I want to say, ask me as many questions as
necessary to ensure
that this concept is tied down.  And
from there, the idea, Fran, is
that you'll also be there this weekend,
based more on what we've
discussed, touching things, trying
things out, modifying things, tinkering,
okay?  So from there on
Monday you and I can talk again
and you can tell me on Monday, okay?  And
on Monday you tell me, "Hey, I'm
thinking about it, I like Odó's stuff."
Let's get to the point.  Okay?  First, the
internal programming and
whether you're interested in using ODO
as a business management system.
Disadvantage, because it is a system that
we have not programmed.  advantage, as
we saw yesterday, because it is a famous system,
right?  From there on, on Monday you can
tell me, "Hey, I've been
looking at it and I don't feel like tying myself
to a software for three months of internships,
so only you can make that final decision
from a technological point of view
and from a Claro point of view
, what's going on?"  Well, in the end,
eh, I insist, eh, Fran, on Monday, with
what you tell me, I'll do it
because, apart from that, eh, let me tell you, I
have two practice groups to
place as DAM, okay?  What's going on?  I'll
give you guys priority, okay?
With which I want to tell you with this that you do
n't feel bad about saying no to me,
because if you say no to me, I, well,
you and Luis, because the two of you are,
let's say, competing for the same
internship position, I don't have much of an idea, I'm
not very clear about whether we're competing
or not, because I don't know if they'll take
one or two, but I want to tell you
that you don't feel bad about saying no at some point
, because if you say
no to me, I'll give him the position.  I
mean, the company to the other group, right?
To DAM group number two and that's it.  I
mean, there's no problem, don't
worry, the company isn't going to
die, so to speak.  But that's what
I'm telling you, okay?  This group has
preference.  What I have first, I
give first to this group.
That said, that said, okay?  This is to
take the pressure off you and so you know that the
decision is in your hands.
Eh, having said that, of course, I see that you, Fran,
from what we've been talking about, not just
these days, but also from what we
talked about last year,
you're a person very interested
in business management systems and in
billing systems and
business management systems.  And from that
perspective, in the same way we
did today, because today with the
XML issue, well, you can have a bit of, as
I would say, a brain explosion, a bit
of a blowout, this can be done.  That
is, we can define the models with
an XML,
right?  I insist, this is the
Jango model from many years ago.
In the same way that you have learned
this today and this knowledge of designing
interfaces with XML and
creating both the view and the model from XML
can give you very good ideas for designing
your own business management systems
,
ODO, that is, spending 3 months
chewing on ODO,
can also give you very good ideas for later,
right?  or stay in ODO and
specialize in ODO and specialize
in providing service to ODO or then
continue designing your own
business management systems, as you already know
I encourage you, but take everything
that you see that works well in
ODO, what you mentioned before that
you really liked the
module system and implement it in your software and
see what is not a [ __ ]
nightmare and not implement it in your
software because you already know that those kinds of
things, x things do not work well, okay?
I tell you, I insist, pros and cons and you
decide, okay?  As for
example, LinkedIn Jobs,
or
Vale, well,
let's see.  No, but this is the
ODO company, right?  This isn't this,
okay?  Although there are currently 166
vacancies.  How brutal.  I didn't know this.
[ __ ].  166 vacancies.
Ah, okay, but no, no.  Yes, yes.  What
things.  It seems like a lot of vacancies,
but well, I didn't expect this.  Okay,
so I had followed.  Ah, no,
this is here.
Here.  Odo has published 176 examples.
Okay, that's interesting.
Oh, no, okay.  Ah, no, yes, yes.  Hear, hear,
hear.
I mean, this will be companies that use
ODO, but I'm not seeing what ODO is.   I'm
telling you, how outrageous.  Which
matches, which matches what we
saw yesterday,
okay?  Or software,
Spain itself,
from 2004 until today, right?  And this is
what there is.   I'm
telling you, okay?  Luis, and you decide, I
tell you, I tell you, Luis, if you decide,
Miguel Ángel, more than anything because of what
we've said these days and these weeks,
that you're on an old-fashioned plan, that is,
when the month of March arrives, okay?
Before March, around January, around there, I will
speak with all of you who are
on the old plan, especially
because you, Miguel Ángel, are obliged
to do the FCTs, so just like
Luis, Fran and Josué, they can and
should start their internships now, okay?
Theoretically they can delay them until
March, but I don't recommend it at
all, okay?  But you, in this case,
Miguel Ángel, I mean that it
seems like I'm ignoring you, but I'm
not ignoring you, but
simply that I have a series of
students who are from a new plan and I
have to place those from a new plan now.
And then I have other students from Plan
Viejo who attend the FCTs from March
to May and therefore it's, in
quotes, nonsense, okay?  I say nonsense,
to use a word, because you should find a
company now when you won't start until March
, because apart from that, what
happens every year happens.  That is, if I
call a company to say, "Hey, I'll
send you a student in 15 days, the company
says, "Okay, tell me." If I send, if
I call a company and say, "I'll
call you to place a student who
will start in March, the company always
tells me, "We'll talk in January, in January or
February."  Okay, that's why I'm telling you that I'm
not going to mention anything to those of you who are old-schoolers
because even if I wanted to
place you, it's going to be pretty impossible,
okay?
And that and that.  So from the point of
view, okay?  We were talking earlier
about Fran's particular interests,
okay?  Now,
from the point of view in which
we are right now, let's say,
within the subject of
intermodular project, well, in
intermodular project in the end what we have to
do is, as we mentioned
before, each one develops a project.
I'm going to go to intermodular project 2,
I'm going to go to any of the
sections.
Okay, so let's wait a moment.
Yes, yes, yes, Fran.  I'm right there.  Yes,
try it.  Yeah.
Oh, man, I didn't know you were staying
close to home.
Well, I didn't know that.
Ah, but of course, Fran.  Ah, well, 23
minutes from home.  Of course, because you lived
in the southern area, in the
southern populated area of ​​Valencia
in Silla.  Exact.  Okay.  So I take it
you're getting the A7,
right?  Chair and well, I hadn't controlled
that issue.
From Silla to Alcudia, which I don't know
if it's the Alcudia of Crespins or who.
And yes, well, 36 minutes or so, yes.  I do
n't know if it's Alcudia, Alcudia
de Crespins or I don't know what.  Ah, the
normal Alcudia.  Okay.
And the Alcudia.
Now yes.  Okay.  And indeed there it
is.
Well, that's it, well, I'm telling you, in fact, what you
just put in your message,
Fran, is literally what it is, okay?
And it's literally what I told you the other
day, which is think about it, look at it,
install it, play with it, try it, and the
decision is yours.  And I tell you, and
nothing happens at all.  Keep in mind that
in this situation, the frying pan
is, I mean, you have a bit of the upper hand
because
a company, which I think I
mentioned to you today, a company that is in
Alcudia, well, with all
my respect and affection for the people of
Alcudia, it probably won't get
as many
candidates as a company that is in
Valencia, okay?  So,
both Luis and you have the strength to do
so.  But indeed, Fran, within
that, I mean, I know what your
interests and your projects are and all that,
uh, and not only do I know it, but I
also celebrate it,
the flexibility and the initiative
you have to create software and all that,
okay?
And of course, giving yourself three months of
internships, during which those three months
would be tied to a specific software
like ODO, isn't frustrating anymore, okay?
But it is something you have to be
aware of, as it would take three months,
I insist, either to specialize in
that software and then dedicate yourself to
it, or three months to get ideas
that you then put into your software.  If you
approach it that way and it works for you, let's go ahead.
And if for whatever reason you say, "[ __ ], I'm
going to die of [ __ ]
disgust with the ear of the lame people in three months, well
, that's it, nothing happens, we move on to
another company, I'm telling you, there are other
candidate companies and nothing happens,
okay?"  And as I was
saying, well
, that's it, from the point of view
of the intermodular project 2, let's
see, we were here the other day in
previous weeks, okay?  Prioritization
of needs.
Okay.  Tax obligations.
One moment.  Okay.
Okay.  Moment.  Sequencing of the Now
I am in intermodular project.  Okay.
Analysis.
Intervention planning.  Okay.
Determination of resources.
evaluation planning.  Okay.
Okay, I'll
tell you.  I'm going to go back and see for a
moment.  And
Correct, correct, correct, Fran,
I totally agree with that.
Yes, yes.  No, that's why, that's why what I
want is for this weekend, I mean,
I leave you alone and you evaluate everything,
effectively.  But it's actually the
same thing I've been telling you all
since the first day of first year in the
databases class: that the
databases class is always
the least popular, but
at the same time, it has advantages.
Uh, this morning I was going to a
class and uh, I mean, I was with some
students to whom I was teaching, I
mean, I was giving them databases and
there was another teacher next to me who
was like, "Ugh, databases, what a drag."
And then another professor who was standing
next to him, who didn't know anything, I'll tell you, this
professor doesn't know anything about databases
because he's not a computer scientist, but he said,
"Yeah, but okay, it's a good idea to
specialize in what's
difficult, because what's difficult is what
people study the least and is what
companies ask for the most."  And I'm
telling you, I turned around and I was like,
"Wow, yeah, you know? Well, that's a
very concise way of putting it. So
that, in this case, ODO, well,
as we've seen, it's on the rise. So,
well, it's kind of disgusting to death
in ODO. When I say disgusting, it's
things like what we've seen today,
right? Why the hell do you redo an
interface system when HTML already exists
, which is the standard for interfaces.
But anyway, one for the other, okay?
I'm not saying anything there, I'll let you do
your thing for the weekend and you, okay? And you'll
see.
Okay, then, I'll tell you, okay? As
for planning the
evaluation,
okay? Once we've proposed, let's
say, a project, let's see, of course, that's it
, but you remember that what you just
said doesn't seem right to me, okay?
In fact, I think what you
just said is really bad,  Fran, because, I mean, I do
n't want you to sell your soul to Google by
improving YouTube and making the
Americans stronger, no, Fran. I
mean, what I want is for you to create
YouTube. And yes, yes, you already knew that, you already
knew that. What I want is for you to create
the Spanish YouTube, okay? And create the
Spanish Google,
but you already knew I was going to say this,
okay? I think you said it to
provoke me. Okay, so,
at this specific point in
evaluation planning, it sounds
bad, okay? Because if you do a
project, how are you going to evaluate that
project? So, to explain this
point, I'm going to explain it to you. It's
perfect for me, thank goodness, considering something that's
been happening to me these days. You see,
you know that I'm
using artificial intelligence software,
and you already know that my project,
Intermodular 2, is
artificial intelligence software for
educational centers, okay?
And you know that software, I'm going
to put it here.
001evaluación.md
md
and I say, I have an AI software
for educational centers, it's
called, you know it, eval.jocarsa.com,
okay? It's like not assuming that the
software is already built, not that it's
built, okay? It's not an
assumption
and it does several things, but let's say it
does two things. One prepares exercises
with artificial intelligence and here comes
the problem.
Okay, it does it with the Quen engine because
when I started designing it, which was the
last weeks of August, well, uh, it
seemed to me to be the best engine, but I made
a mistake
here in class, I'm telling you, and that is that, uh, I did
n't consider
alternatives,
okay? And then it evaluates uh
with
Quen, it
calls and and which one else do I use. You have it in
the corrections. Uh, Chinese calls
and and gema, the one from Google. Okay,
here I did consider alternatives
and in fact I took the plunge because
the first days of the tests
I evaluated with Quen and I said, "Look, I don't
trust it." Okay, the  Regarding the topic of preparing
exercises, well, okay, but
I need that if a student is evaluated, that they are
evaluated in the best possible way,
okay? So, what I did
next was to put in three
different artificial intelligences, like let's say
three different people, and give you the
best grade, okay? Which in fact is
usually the one that gives the best grade.
From here on, from here on, I only
tried these three alternatives. What am I
finding?
I'm finding
that some of
the exercises
slip up from time to time,
okay? Statements that from time to time you
tell me, "Hey, this statement I'm
getting is weird or it asks for
strange things or it's not appropriate." And there are times when
I say, "No, no, no, it's correct,
read it better." But there are other times when
I say, "No, no, no, it's messed up, tell me
what activity it is and I'll delete it and
regenerate it." Okay? And then the evaluation
that I keep tweaking
as
the students give me feedback.
Okay, the evaluation
of  Every now and then, either she doesn't reason
correctly,
or, let's say, she takes points off
for things she shouldn't. So yesterday
morning, a student looked at me with her
laptop and said, "Hey, he
said something during the marking." And
I said, "Damn, he shouldn't have told you that
." Okay, so, so
I came here, I came to Eval,
I came to useful, I came to Evalúa.
Here it is, okay? And I said, "
Students are not required to
title their submission.  Don't take away points
for this reason." Okay? Because a
student said, "He took away
points because he told me I didn't
include a title, when at no
point in the evaluation rubric does it say
that I have to include a title." And
I told her, "Well look, no, he
made up the title thing there and simply for
future evaluations, I tell him,
don't take away points for not including a title."
Okay? This is what I mean by
evaluation. I mean, evaluation sounds
strange in that you evaluate your own
project and then you'll
say, "Well, I evaluate the project and
what do I do? I give myself a 10, I give myself a
five, I give myself a seven." It's not that. It's
evaluation as uh introspection
and continuous improvement.
What is one of the tasks that I'm going to
do this weekend? And what I
'm going to tell you is, I swear, 100% real.
Well, this weekend I'm doing an
evaluation task. Yes, yes,  I know, I know
, I know, I know, I know, I know. It's that,
that, that, Fran. That's exactly what you
're saying is what I'm referring to,
okay? Where step number one, we'll
talk now, okay? What you're
saying is step number two. He
always tells me, "The conclusion is brief
and you have to do such and such." And sometimes it's true,
but sometimes there are students who come to me and
say, "Hey, it's just that, damn, I've made an
effort." And I read this and say,
"It's true, I mean, there's the
artificial intelligence." Well, whether you like it or not, you like it or not, it's
doing, I insist,
99% of things right, but that 1% of
things that it does wrong, well, it attacks you a
little, okay? Which seems fine to me.
So, localhost/eval/admin.
I also think that's why, so that you know that I
have it here, okay? This here that
is sending to the trash and adding
human evaluation, okay? So that
you can always rest assured that
the human  It can do more than the machine, right?
Let's see.
Okay. Okay. Introduction 20,
okay? And it doesn't give you 25. I know, I know, I
know. I'm telling you, I have a lot of
students like that. Conclusion 18, the
conclusion is brief and links to the
unit, although it could be more detailed.
Okay,
so, Fran, what's
happening? Well, evaluation, okay? I
simply have to continuously evaluate
the development, okay? The
performance of my application.
I evaluate the performance,
uh, I analyze
the deficiencies, the shortcomings or the
opportunities for improvement
and I
plan
how to evaluate
and analyze and how to improve.
What am I going to do? I insist, I
mean, this isn't just talk. I
swear I'm going to do this this
weekend. I haven't done it during the week
because life doesn't allow me, okay?
But I'm going to do it on the weekend,
which is when I have more hours. What I
'm going to do is, I'm
going to take
a series of  uh,
sample of one or more.
I said before, okay? That right now she's
preparing it with Quen
B. I
'm going to unload. This isn't
a future project I'd do, right? It's a
project that's already underway, and in
fact, it's very much underway. There are a ton
of you students working on that project. I
'm going to unload
all the SIAS I
can,
and C. I'm
going to feed that rubric or that exercise or those
exercises
to the IAS,
and D. I'm going to check
which AI produces the best
statements. Okay. And
yes, Fran, exactly, exactly. Okay, exactly,
okay?
That's exactly the point, which is what I
was telling you yesterday, that it's not that I have a
grudge against the United States, on the contrary,
okay? Uh, I don't know if you're saying this
to tease me, to provoke me, okay?
But it's what I was telling you yesterday, I mean, I
don't have a grudge against the United States, I
admire it, I respect it, I
envy the United States,
because Fran, I don't know if you're saying this
as a joke, but it's true.  I mean, but for
a very simple reason,
because at a given moment, Open goes to the United
States, that is, to the United
States government, I insist,
Sam Altman,
Donald Trump.
I mean, what I'm going to
tell you, I'm not making this up, you'll
see.
Let's see
a moment. Images. This.
Okay, just a moment.
And
let's see.
Okay. And then, I insist, Donald Trump or
anyone or Biden, okay?
previously, comes along
and sees that there's an American company
that needs millions to
develop the best
artificial intelligence, and not just Donald Trump, but
the people behind it tell him,
"Hey, give this guy money, because if you
give this guy money, we're going to
lead this market, and this market is
very important in the future from a
strategic point of view." And any
president of the United States comes along and
says, "Tell me how many millions you need, and I
'll give you three times as many millions
as you ask for." In exchange for what? In
exchange for technological supremacy
remaining within this country. And that's
what I admire about the United States.  And that
's what we don't have here in Spain, nor are we
going to have in principle. I mean,
imagine it, okay? Imagine
this photo. You see this photo and say,
well, that's it. Typical, in the United States
they support technology. Typical, okay?
Imagine that photo in Spain and it would be
laughable. I mean, I usually imagine it would be
laughable because that's unthinkable. Okay?
So, of course, but the problem,
Miguel Ángel,
isn't that the United States has a
monopoly on everything, especially
technology.
The problem is that we let them.
I mean, they do what they have to
do, they do what we
should be doing and aren't
doing. Okay? Indeed
, indeed, whenever someone appears,
as you mentioned, Fran, who
isn't a politician, but rather a
technologist,
someone who isn't involved in the
political wheel, but rather someone who you
say, "Look, well, the minister of
universities, well, hey, he's an
astronaut, damn, super cool, right?"  It doesn't last
long, indeed.  And then another type
of politician, we all know what I
mean, but I'm not going to say it, and
I'm not talking about one party or
another, but about all of them at once. Well, those
types of politicians last much longer
because politics in this country
is made like that, right?  So that's why I'm
saying that Fran, I don't know
if you said it as a joke or not, but it's
true that the best
artificial intelligences are in the United
States and it's not by chance,
but it's simply a matter of millions
and so directly.  And
when Google is giving us
gem and Meta is giving us flame for
free, that's how it is, you
can imagine that what they are
giving us is 1% of what they have in
their facilities, obviously, right?
and it is totally normal.  So that's why
I insist that I always give the
impression that I'm anti-United States,
and quite the opposite.  I mean, I think
they are the model that we
should follow and that we don't follow in the
end.  Well, as for the
assessment task, well, the second
assessment activity I'm going to do this
weekend is to assess the assessment, that is
, to assess myself.  Okay?
So, assessment evaluation task
.
Well Fran, this is exactly what you just
said, that is, checking if the AI ​​is
evaluating correctly.
Uh, to see if instead
of a committee of three experts,
things improve or not if I put five
experts on it.
That is, when I say evaluation, I don't
mean that I, as a teacher, am going to
evaluate your projects, right?  Because
in this project, imagine that I'm not
there.  What this means is that
you yourselves must establish
policies and actions to evaluate
your own project, which is something that is
always very lazy.
In my case, the evaluation is
purely a matter of
necessity, because I have students
telling me, "Hey, there are activities
that are a pain."  And I have students telling me
exactly what you told me,
Fran.  Hey, the feedback you're giving me does
n't seem accurate.  So,
in my case, evaluation, self-criticism, and improvement are mandatory,
which is why I say I have to do it.
Enough.  So, uh, sure, well, no no
no that thing about it not having that much
infinite memory, right?  I mean, I'm telling you, he
has it.  The only thing is that it doesn't
let you send more than I don't know how many tokens
a day or every x hours, but it
has memory.  So, of course, this is what I
was telling you, that in the United States it is Yes,
yes, GPT chat, I'll give it to you for free, but in
exchange you give me your information.
Tell me what you ask, tell me what you
ask.  Mind you, for example, I told you
that all the answers you're
sending
are, as I would say, the
training
of an artificial intelligence that
we will train at the end of the course, okay?
I can tell you that this
artificial intelligence will be cow dung.  I'll
tell you why.
Because right now, right now in
activities,
let's see,
in activities right now there are
items, okay?
This means that if the course lasts,
imagine 10 months, which it doesn't last 10
months, then in the end it would have 40,000
exercises, let's say 50,000 exercises.
I come to GPT chat, I'll do it more as a
demonstration than anything else
and I say, uh, my students are submitting
activities
with which uh at the end of the course I will
use their
JSON files to perform
a fine tune
of an AI like Quen.
I estimate
that by the end of the course I will have about
50,000 activities
submitted.
And
that will improve Quen's efficiency in
solving
problems.
of programming.
I've asked this question before, I'm
warning you.
Let's see.
Good question.  It depends on what you mean
by efficiency.  Okay,
okay.
Yes, it will probably improve accuracy.
If
the 50,000 activities are clean, they
are diverse and have
verified correct solutions.   That
is, assuming that everyone
will get a 10, which is not going to happen.
Good.  You format each example as an
instruction, input, and output.  If
possible.
Specific domains, yes, with your
formats, your rubric, your language, your
style, okay?  No, not my style, but
hey, enough.
More consistent answers
, better success rates, and fewer
hallucinations.
No, it doesn't reduce latency, I don't care about that
, okay?  Hey, how do you get the
most out of it?  Creating JSONL, okay?
and okay, training strategy with a
butt and okay and okay, come on, very good.
Metrics,
eh, if the
base
eh is a let's say 100%,
after that fine tune of 50,000 1000
questions.
Hey, what would the
power percentage be?  Okay, power is a
very, very abstract term in this case.
Or how many exercises would be
needed to reach 200% of, so to
speak, power.
Now Charl GPT will tell me, "This
power thing is very like this, okay?"  But well,
but let's say 200% knowledge,
expertise,
let's see.
Okay, power doesn't follow a
linear relationship, that's very clear.  Okay, I'm
telling you, I know what he's going to
answer because I've asked him
several times in the last month.
Okay?  So, uh, short and to the point.  There
is no linear power percentage.   I
know, that's why I put it in
quotes, because okay, it's a very
similar term, okay?  And let's see,
okay, with a conservative,
okay?  A typical plus 10 20 points,
okay?  Okay.  Well, 10 20 points.
How many would be needed for 200%
power?  If 200 means doubling the
success, correct?  Okay?  In that case,
okay, you'll need orders of magnitude
more data,
hundreds of thousands to millions, I mean,
ongoing,
yes, but well, yes, no, Fran, I mean,
I'm totally aware of what you
're saying, okay?  I also tell you
one thing and that is that in these previous weeks
and every time I ask HGPT, how would
I tell you, right?  Nonsense,
Python libraries, Python instructions,
JavaScript stuff, it's like the
answer is quick and to the point.  The
moment I ask Chat GPT
questions about me building the
AI, it
seems like it refuses to give the
answers, you know?  I don't know if you know or can
imagine why that might be, but oh well.
So, I want to tell you that what you
just said, don't worry, I
have it in my mind at all times,
okay?  But it's to ask a question, let
's say, first and foremost, because
something is something and I always know that
an American AI is answering me
about a Chinese one.  I could
ask the same thing about llama, you know?
Good.  So basically what
I want to tell you is this, okay?  It's that
with a knowledge base of 50,000
activities at most, right?  Well if I
want to duplicate it I would need
hundreds of thousands to millions.  What I want to
tell you with this is that training,
okay?  The training we're going to
do, well, we'll do it at the end of the
course, will serve to explain
how to collect data, that
is, collected data, how to collect
healthy data and use it to do
training.  Regarding training, by
the way, I'd like to take this opportunity to tell you that either we
do it on a GPU or it could take
weeks,
and then we'll have improved
the artificial intelligence a bit, okay?  But
when I say a little, I mean it
will be a little noticeable, but don't
think it will be a lot, okay?  So the
idea of ​​this point is this.  The idea of
this point.  Let's see.
Yeah, no, I mean,
but wait, and you log off?  What
do you mean?
Okay, because I mean, more than you
disconnect it will be Ah, yes, yes, correct,
correct.  In my case, on my PC I do
n't think so much, I don't know, but of course,
when you're using a
North American AI and you use Windows or Mac,
which are
North American operating systems,
then if your PC suddenly turns off,
well it wouldn't be so strange, it would be, okay,
probably probably eh
Look, look, wait,
look.  Look,
eh,
now you'll see this.  I don't know if I've ever
taught it to you.
Prepare
the report
that you think the FIA ​​NSA FBI may have
on me based on the information you know
and the information that can be
found about me.
Okay?  Let's see.  Ah, look, well
look, now it says for ethical or
legal reasons, but a hypothetical example.
Look, hypothetical example or he has been
left hanging.  This is what you were saying
a moment ago.  Now he says about
ethical or legal reasons.  Before
summer I would give you the
report directly.
Now you'll see.
Well, he's literally
stuck.  I'm going to refresh.
M.
[Music]